const oysterQuestions = [

    {
        count: 1,
        question: "Which goddess from Greek mythology emerged from the sea on an oyster shell?",
        answers: [
            "Aphrodite",
            "Minerva",
            "Athena"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Aphrodite"
    },

    {
        count: 2,
        question: "Ostreidae is the scientific name for the edible oyster. Which genus is that of the pearl-forming oysters?",
        answers: [
            "Mollusc",
            "Crassostrea",
            "Pinctada"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Pinctada"
    },

    {
        count: 3,
        question: "The largest oysters can grow up to three feet long in shell length. Which is the largest pearl-producing oyster?",
        answers: [
            "Akoya oyster",
            "Black-winged pearl oyster",
            "Silver-lipped oyster"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Silver-lipped oyster"
    },

    {
        count: 4,
        question: "The oyster crab is also known as which?",
        answers: [
            "Lobster crab",
            "Cucumber crab",
            "Pea crab"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Pea crab"
    },

    {
        count: 5,
        question: "What is an oyster?",
        answers: [
            "An insect",
            "An arachnid",
            "A mollusc"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "A mollusc"
    },

    {
        count: 6,
        question: "Which family do True oysters belong to?",
        answers: [
            "Spondylus",
            "Ostreidae",
            "Pteriidae"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Ostreidae"
    },

    {
        count: 7,
        question: "How long does it take for oysters to reach their maturity?",
        answers: [
            "Two years",
            "Six months",
            "One year"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "One year"
    },

    {
        count: 8,
        question: "Which is the most widely grown bivalve around the world?",
        answers: [
            "The Sydney rock oyster",
            "The Olympia oyster",
            "The Pacific oyster"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "The Pacific oyster"
    },

    {
        count: 9,
        question: "In which year was the eastern oyster introduced into the waters of California?",
        answers: [
            "1929",
            "1935",
            "1875"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "1875"
    },

    {
        count: 10,
        question: "What elements does the oyster contain?",
        answers: [
            "Calcium",
            "Zinc",
            "Both are true"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Both are true"
    },

    {
        count: 11,
        question: "What is a group of oyster called?",
        answers: [
            "Oyster group",
            "Oyster reef",
            "Oyster family"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Oyster reef"
    },

    {
        count: 12,
        question: "How can oysters be eaten?",
        answers: [
            "Smoked",
            "Boiled",
            "Both are correct"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Both are correct"
    },

    {
        count: 13,
        question: "What is the process of opening the oyster called?",
        answers: [
            "Oyster-open",
            "Oyster-shucking",
            "Killing oyster"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Oyster-shucking"
    },

    {
        count: 14,
        question: "Which ancient civilization was the first to cultivate oysters?",
        answers: [
            "Romans",
            "Egyptians",
            "Greeks"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Greeks"
    },

    {
        count: 15,
        question: "During which period did oysters experience a surge in production?",
        answers: [
            "18th and 19th centuries",
            "12th and 13th centuries",
            "20th and 21st centuries"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "18th and 19th centuries"
    },
];